AoM Records 5289
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series SERIES I. ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS
  - Sub-Series G. PROFESSIONAL DIVISIONS.
    - Sub-Series 5. Human Resources Division
      - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Newsletter (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Sub-Series 6. International Management Division
      - Governance, General Policy Statement, Membership Form, Position Paper (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - Governance, Membership Survey, Sub-area Interest Form, Five-year audit (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - Annual Meeting, Call for Doctoral Consortium nominations (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - Annual Meeting, Call for papers (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - Annual Meeting Annual Meeting Schedule, Call for reviewers (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - Membership Committee, Directory, Call for Membership, Survey, Roster (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Elections Committee, Ballots, and Biographies (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Elections Committee, Ballots, and Biographies (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 19, Folder 31)
      - Research Committee, directory, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 32)
      - Research Committee, Highlights of current and completed research projects (Box 19, Folder 33)
      - Newsletters, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 34)
      - Newsletters, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 35)
      - Newsletters, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 35a)
      - Newsletters, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 36)
      - Newsletters, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 37)
      - Newsletters, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 38)
      - Newsletters, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 39)
      - Newsletters, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 40)
      - Newsletters, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 41)
      - Newsletters, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 42)
      - Newsletters, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 43)
      - Newsletters, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 44)
      - Newsletters, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 45)
      - Newsletters, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 46)
      - Newsletters, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 47)
      - Newsletters, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Sub-Series 7. Managerial Education and Development Division
      - Governance (Box 19, Folder 49)
      - Elections (Box 19, Folder 50)
      - Correspondence (Box 19, Folder 50)
      - Newsletter, 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 50)
      - Newsletter, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 51)
      - Newsletter, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 52)
      - Newsletter, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 53)
      - Newsletter, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 54)
      - Newsletter, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 55)
      - Newsletter, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 56)
      - Newsletter, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 57)
      - Newsletter, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 58)
      - Newsletter, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Sub-Series 8. Management History Division
      - Committee on Management History, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Governance, First Organizational Meeting, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Governance, Steering Committee (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Governance, Constitution Committee, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Governance, Constitution and By-Laws, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Governance, List of Officers and Publications of Interest, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Second Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1973-1986 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Program, Annual Meeting, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Program, Annual Meeting, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Program, Annual Meeting, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Program, Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Program, Annual Meeting, 1984-1988 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Annual Meeting, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Program, Annual Meeting, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Award to Y. Avishai, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Tribute Dinner for John Mee, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 17)
        Aug-78
      - Proposal for Centennial Celebration, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Research Conference on Management History, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Formation of Working Paper Series, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Working Paper Series, Policy Guidelines, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Working Paper, "Education, Business Education, Management Education." (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Working Paper, "Institutional Participation in AOM...", 1976 (Box 20, Folder 23)
      - Working Paper, "Management Historian as a Detective." (Box 20, Folder 24)
      - Working Paper, "Pioneers in Personnel...", 1977 (Box 20, Folder 25)
      - Working Paper, "Wills as a Source of Historical Evidence" (Box 20, Folder 26)
      - Working Paper Series, correspondence (Box 20, Folder 27)
      - Working Paper, "Symposium on Committee on Human Relations Industry" (Box 20, Folder 28)
      - Membership Committee, 1983-1988 (Box 20, Folder 29)
      - Membership Committee, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 30)
      - Membership Lists, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 31)
      - Elections, Ballots and Results, 1976-1986 (Box 20, Folder 32)
      - Elections, Ballots, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 41)
      - Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 42)
      - Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 43)
      - Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 44)
      - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 45)
      - Correspondence, Wren-Pollard, 1979-1982 (Box 20, Folder 46)
      - Correspondence, 1980-1984 (Box 20, Folder 47)
      - Correspondence, 1987-1996 (Box 20, Folder 48)
      - Research, F. W. Taylor, Letter and Manuscript of "Faith Not Facts..." (Box 20, Folder 49)
      - Research, F. W. Taylor, general correspondence, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 50)
      - Research, F. W. Taylor, The "Search for Schmidt", 1976 (Box 20, Folder 51)
      - Research, F. W. Taylor, general correspondence, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 52)
      - Research, F. W. Taylor, General Correspondence, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 53)
      - Research, F. W. Taylor, General Correspondence and "Cooke Creates a Classic", 1977 (Box 20, Folder 54)
      - Research, F. W. Taylor, General Correspondence and Letters from Sanford Thompson to Taylor, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 55)
      - N-File, correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 20, Folder 56)
      - N-File, Wrege's Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 57)
      - N-File, Wrege - Van Fleet correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 20, Folder 58)
      - International Standard Serial Number, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 59)
      - N-File #1, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 60)
        Original
      - N-File #2 and #3, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 61)
      - N-File #4 and #5, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 62)
      - N-File #6 and #7, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 63)
      - N-File #8, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 64)
        Spring 1977
      - N-File #9 and #10, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 65)
        Summer - Fall, 1977
      - N-File #11, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 66)
        Nov. 1977
      - N-File #12 and #13, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 67)
      - N-File #14, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 68)
        Oct-78
      - N-File #15, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 69)
        Feb-79
      - N-File #16, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 70)
        Apr-79
      - N-File #18, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 71)
        Feb-80
      - N-File #19, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 72)
        Jul-80
      - N-File #20, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 73)
        Oct-80
      - N-File #21, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 74)
        Feb-81
      - N-File #22, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 75)
        Apr-81
      - N-File #23, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 76)
        October 1981
      - N-File #24, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 77)
        Feb-82
      - N-File #25, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 78)
        Apr-82
      - N-File #26, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 79)
        Oct-82
      - N-File #28, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 80)
        Apr-83
      - N-File #29, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 81)
        Nov-83
      - N-File #30, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 82)
        Feb-84
      - N-File #31, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 83)
        Apr-84
      - N-File #32, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 84)
        Nov-84
      - N-File #33, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 85)
        Feb-85
      - N-File #34, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 86)
        Apr-85
      - N-File #35, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 87)
        Nov-85
      - N-File #36, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 88)
        Feb-86
      - N-File #37, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 89)
        Apr-86
      - N-File Material from D. Van Fleet as Editor, 1976-1978 (Box 20, Folder 90)
      - D. Van Fleet, N-File Editor, correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 20, Folder 91)
      - Newsletter Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 92)
      - Newsletters, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 93)
      - Newsletters, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 94)
      - Newsletters, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 95)
      - Newsletters, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 96)
      - Newsletters, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 97)
      - Newsletters, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 98)
      - Newsletters, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 99)
      - Newsletters, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 100)
      - Newsletters, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 101)
      - Newsletters, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 102)
      - Newsletters, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 103)
      - Newsletters, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 104)
      - Newsletters, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 105)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 106)
      - Bibliography of Theses and Dissertations (Box 20, Folder 107)
    - Sub-Series 9. Unprocessed Materials
      - Academy of Management Review (Box 21, Folder All)
        Publication Files
      - Academy of Management Review (Box 22, Folder All)
      - Academy of Management Review (Box 23, Folder All)
        Publication Files. Varying divisions' files, publications, correspondence. Also includes AOM Review articles, papers, and correspondence with AOM Review authors
      - Dues Books and Videotapes(2) (Box 24, Folder All)
      - Academy of Management, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 1)
        National Meeting, O. B. Presentation Paperwork & Related Items
      - O. B. Division, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 2)
        1977 National Meeting of AOM, Various paperwork from 1976 National Meeting, Post 1977 OBD Divisional Paperwork
      - J. G. Hunts, OBD Files, 1975-1977 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Academy of Management National Meeting, OBD / Related OBD papers, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Academy of Management, OB - Division Evaluations (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - J. G. Hunt: 1977 AOM Meetings, OB Division Planning Materials (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Archival Materials from Organizational Behavior Division of Academy, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, OB Division Membership List, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - OB Reviewers Manual, Rejection and Accepting Notices, Lists of Papers, Reviewers Comments, correspondence concerning the 1979 Atlanta Monthly Meeting of the OB Division (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Ballots, correspondence, OB papers and Reviewers Comments (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, OB Newsletters, Program Committee OB Division List, Reviewers Comments, Ballots and Questionnaires, 1982- 2004 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Change Research Network Information, correspondence (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Division of Organization and Management Theory paper evaluation forms, correspondence, ballots, newsletters, list of members, 1974- 1986 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Organizational Information System Interest Group (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Minutes (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Originals of "PLOM Perspectives" when Gore was Chair and Editor of that Division, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - George Gore, on Production Operations Management Division, 1970-1976 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Proposal for Divisional Status, correspondence (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Managerial Consultation Division, Governance, Constitutional Changes, 5 year Review, Surveys (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Managerial Consultation Division, Academy of Annual Meeting, Calls for Papers, Invitations (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Managerial Consultation Division, Membership Committee, Directory, New Member forms (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Managerial Consultation Division, Elections Committee, Ballots, Biographies, Nominations (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Managerial Consultation Division, Elections Committee, Ballots, Biographies, Nominations (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - Managerial Consultation Division, correspondence, Academy Divisions and Managerial Consultation Division membership (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Managerial Consultation Division, correspondence, AMCF, consulting survey (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Public and Nonprofit Division, Governance (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Public and Nonprofit Division, Annual Meeting, Calls for Papers, 1986-1993 (Box 25, Folder 27)
      - Public and Nonprofit Division, Annual Meeting, Calls for Papers, 1993-1996 (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Public and Nonprofit Division, Membership Committee, Application for Academy of Management, Directories, 1980-1992 (Box 25, Folder 29)
      - Public and Nonprofit Division, Elections Committee, Nomination & Election ballots, 1980-1992 (Box 25, Folder 30)
      - Public and Nonprofit Division, Elections Committee, Misc. Dates, Nomination & Election ballots, 1993-1999 (Box 25, Folder 31)
      - Ballots and correspondence (Box 25, Folder 32)
      - Operations Management Division (Box 25, Folder 33)
      - Questionnaires for the Organization of Management Theory Division (Box 25, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence, ballots, misc. (Box 25, Folder 35)
      - OB Ballots, conference programs, 1987-1997 (Box 25, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence, ballots (Box 25, Folder 37)
      - Ballots, correspondence, misc. (Box 25, Folder 38)
      - Ballots, Nomination forms, correspondence, miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 39)
      - S. I. M. Constitution Information (Box 25, Folder 40)
      - Miscellaneous, ballots, and correspondence (Box 25, Folder 41)
      - Academy of Management Rankings, folder 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Academy of Management Rankings, folder 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - AMR Manuscripts, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Academy of Management, Management History - OB Sympos, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - OB Division - Academy, folder 1 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - OB Division - Academy, folder 2 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - MGF: Academy of: papers, etc. folder 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - MGF: Academy of: papers, etc. folder 2 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - MGT: Academy of: Annual Reports and Agendas (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - MGT: Academy of: Reviews and "Social Psychological Control" papers (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Reviewer Comments (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Reviews, AMR Manuscripts, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - AMR Manuscripts (Box 26, Folder 13)
        Numbers: 32, 33, and 33R, 40, and R469, 76 - 174R
      - AMR Manuscripts (Box 26, Folder 14)
        Numbers: 77-88, 77 - 105B, 77 - 111R, 77-166, 77-219, 77-179, 77-183, 7 7-243, and 77-243R, 77-250
      - AMR Manuscripts (Box 26, Folder 15)
        Numbers:78-145, 78-163, 78-187, and 185R, 78-209 and 209R, 78-216
      - AMR Manuscripts (Box 26, Folder 16)
        Numbers: 78-248, 29-21, and 21R and 21RR, 79-25, and 25R, 79-43, 79-105, and 105R
      - AMR Manuscripts (Box 26, Folder 17)
        Numbers: 77-254-254RR, 77-285, 78-12, 78-25, and 54R, 78-92, 78-139
      - AMR Manuscripts (Box 26, Folder 18)
        Numbers:79-124, 79-159, 79-210, 79-254, 79-264, 80-184RR, 81-70R, 81-90, 81-93, 81-100
      - Unnumbered Manuscripts from AMR, misc. reviews, notes, correspondence, and bibliography (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Academy of Management Financial Statements, Annual Reports, 1978-1988 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Academy of Management Financial Statements, Annual Reports, AOM Passbooks, 1948-1989 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Information on the American Management Association (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Newspaper articles, photos and negatives, a plastic bag, business cards, correspondences, applications, newsletters, bulletins, invitations, essays, magazine articles, brochures, blank certificates (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Information on the Institute for Administrative Research (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Scholarship and other awards (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Financial Information, Academy of Management, 1951-1989 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Sigma Iota Epsilon Information (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Newsletters and Reviews (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Proceedings of the Annual Meetings, 1959-1970 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Academy of Management Newsletter, correspondence, 1974-1989 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Information about the Academy of Management Review and Academy of Management Editor, correspondence (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Surveys / ballots (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous / correspondence (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Constitutional Information for the Fellows, 1953-1993 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Fellows - policies and mission statement (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Annual Meetings Information, folder 1 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Annual Meetings Information, folder 2 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Election Information - Fellows, 1958-1994 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Fellows Nominations, 1969-1981 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Fellows Nominations, 1982-1994 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Fellows Committees - Fellows selection, membership policy, exceptional candidates, 1988-1991 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Fellows selection procedures and membership forms, dues implementation and financial statements, correspondence, 1960-1993 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Fellows Rosters, 1948-1993 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - J. P. Worthy (Box 28, Folder 11)
        Fellows Records and Correspondence
      - J. P. Worthy, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 12)
        Fellows correspondence
      - Fellows - rosters, records, correspondence, related to reconstructing Fellows history (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence for and by Karl Reyer on the Fellows (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Fellows information - from files of Joe Towle (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence from and to Larry Cummings - Fellows (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - Fellows Seal and Emblem (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - The Management Oar Newsletter - Fellows (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - Fellows election, selection, and correspondence (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence from and to Arthur Bedeian - Fellows, correspondence from and to Jack Duncan (Box 28, Folder 20)
      - Academy of Management Memorandums, Growth and size of the Academy Information, conference notices, correspondence, division counts (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Program chairs, correspondence, ballots, territorial domain statements (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Various Papers on Social Issues in Management Division, 1982-1991 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Report on the Women in Management Interest Group (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Directory of people involved with WIM, status of Women Report, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Women in Management Newsletter, miscellaneous correspondence about WIM. (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Academy of Management Newsletter, the Institute of Behavioral and Applied Management (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - GBA update (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Advertisement for University of Nebraska (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Annual Meeting of the Academy of Management - San Diego, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 10)
        Call For Papers, symposium, and workshops
      - Chicago conference, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Giants in Management (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Papers by David C. Moore (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Papers by Burleigh B. Gardner, folder 1 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Papers by Burleigh B. Gardner, folder 2 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - Papers by James C. Worthy, folder 1 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Papers by James C. Worthy, folder 2 (Box 29, Folder 17)
      - Letters from Jeff Sonnenfeld (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - Emerging Management Realities, correspondence (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - Public Review Board appeals (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - Call for Papers, O. N. E. Newsletter, collegiate entrepreneurs organization, qualitative research, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Organizational Communication and Information Systems Group, Inc. (Box 29, Folder 22)